A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Fourth Administration, Subseries 37.4 FA439C
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fourth Administration, 1971-1973; 4; 114 microform reels
  - Executive Clemency (Reel 31, Reel 32)
    - Edward Weis (Reel 32, Frame 64)
    - General (Reel 32, Frame 69)
  - Extradition (Reel 32)
    - Robert Apablaza (Reel 32, Frame 127)
    - Nick Donald Bagley (Reel 32, Frame 129)
    - General (Reel 32, Frame 131)
  - Fiscal (Reel 32, Reel 33, Reel 34, Reel 35, Reel 36, Reel 37, Reel 38, Reel 39)
    - Accounting & Auditing (Reel 32, Reel 33, Reel 34, Reel 35, Reel 36)
      - Department of Audit & Control (Reel 32, Reel 33, Reel 34, Reel 35, Reel 36)
        - Audit Reports
          - 1973 August-October (Reel 32, Frame 150)
          - 1973 February 6-September (Reel 33, Frame 16)
          - 1973 February 6-September (Reel 34, Frame 15)
          - 1971 August 24-1972 May (Reel 35, Frame 16)
          - 1971 January-August (Reel 36, Frame 16)
      - Financial Analysis Statements (Reel 36, Frame 210)
      - General (Reel 36, Frame 224)
    - Budget (Reel 36, Reel 37)
      - Division of (Reel 36, Frame 225)
      - Yearly Budget
        - 1972-1973 (Reel 36, Frame 226)
        - 1971 (Reel 37, Frame 17)
      - General (Reel 37, Frame 66)
      - Expenditures (Reel 37, Frame 73)
    - Revenue
      - Department of Tax & Finance (Reel 37)
        - Commendation (Reel 37, Frame 74)
        - Income Tax Bureau (Reel 37, Frame 76)
        - Lottery (Reel 37, Frame 77)
        - General (Reel 37, Frame 110)
      - General (Reel 37, Reel 38, Reel 39)
        - Cigarette Tax (Reel 37, Frame 114)
        - Income Tax (Reel 37, Frame 140)
        - Property Tax (Reel 37, Frame 165)
        - Revenue Sharing
          - A-Z (Reel 37, Frame 192)
          - Flat List (Reel 37, Frame 218)
          - Flat List (Reel 38, Frame 15)
        - General (Reel 38, Frame 20)
        - Gasoline Tax (Reel 38, Frame 228)
        - Insurance Taxation (Reel 38, Frame 229)
        - Sales Tax (Reel 38, Frame 232)
        - Unincorporated Business Tax
          - 1973 (Reel 38, Frame 251)
          - 1971-1972 (Reel 39, Frame 14)
        - Miscellaneous (Reel 39, Frame 21)
    - General (Reel 39)
      - Resolution (Reel 39, Frame 73)
      - Miscellaneous (Reel 39, Frame 151)
  - Fund Raising (Reel 39)
    - American Cancer Society (Reel 39, Frame 164)
    - Arthritis (Reel 39, Frame 170)
    - Cerebral Palsy (Reel 39, Frame 172)
    - United Fund - Red Cross (Reel 39, Frame 174)
    - Cystic Fibrosis (Reel 39, Frame 217)
    - Heart Fund (Reel 39, Frame 219)
    - Mental Health Appeal (Reel 39, Frame 219)
    - Multiple Sclerosis (Reel 39, Frame 221)
    - Muscular Dystrophy (Reel 39, Frame 223)
    - Others (Reel 39, Frame 224)
    - General (Reel 39, Frame 227)
  - Gambling (Reel 39)
    - Gambling (Reel 39, Frame 228)
  - General Services (Reel 39, Reel 40)
    - Offices of (Reel 39)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 39, Frame 236)
    - Central Operations (Reel 39)
      - State Cars (Reel 39, Frame 236)
    - Real Property Management (Reel 39)
      - Brooklyn State Office Building (Reel 39, Frame 252)
    - Central Operations (Reel 40)
      - General (Reel 40, Frame 14)
    - Real Property Management (Reel 40)
      - Capitol (Reel 40, Frame 18)
      - Harcorn State Office Building (Reel 40, Frame 22)
      - International Symbol of Access (Reel 40, Frame 27)
      - General (Reel 40, Frame 29)
    - Standards & Purchases (Reel 40)
      - Bottled Water (Reel 40, Frame 49)
      - Construction Institute Format (Reel 40, Frame 52)
      - Contracts Bidding (Reel 40, Frame 54)
      - Contracts Bidding Agreement (Reel 40, Frame 73)
      - General (Reel 40, Frame 78)
    - General (Reel 40, Frame 89)
  - Government (Reel 40, Reel 41, Reel 42, Reel 43, Reel 44, Reel 45, Reel 46, Reel 47, Reel 48)
    - Federal (Reel 40, Reel 41, Reel 42)
      - Agriculture (Reel 40, Frame 92)
      - Census (Reel 40, Frame 100)
      - Commerce (Reel 40, Frame 104)
      - Defense (Reel 40, Frame 109)
      - General Service Administration (Reel 40, Frame 115)
      - Health Education & Welfare (Reel 40, Frame 118)
      - Housing (Reel 40, Frame 146)
      - Immigration & Naturalization (Reel 40, Frame 165)
      - Inauguration (Reel 40, Frame 187)
      - Interior (Reel 40, Frame 192)
      - Justice (Reel 40, Frame 193)
      - Labor (Reel 40, Frame 197)
      - Office of Economic Opportunity (OEO)
        - 1973 (Reel 40, Frame 206)
        - 1971-1972 (Reel 41, Frame 15)
      - Post Office (Reel 41)
        - Commemorative Stamp (Reel 41, Frame 107)
        - General (Reel 41, Frame 120)
      - President's Economic Policy (Reel 41, Frame 138)
      - Office of the President (Reel 41, Frame 210)
      - Small Business Administration (Reel 41, Frame 216)
      - State (Reel 41, Frame 241)
      - Transportation (Reel 41, Frame 246)
      - Treasury (Reel 41, Frame 251)
      - Visa & Passport (Reel 42, Frame 17)
      - White House Fellows Program (Reel 42, Frame 40)
      - General (Reel 42, Frame 60)
    - International (Reel 42, Reel 43)
      - Brazil (Reel 42, Frame 148)
      - Canada (Reel 42, Frame 150)
      - China (Reel 42, Frame 153)
      - Cuba (Reel 42, Frame 157)
      - France (Reel 42, Frame 158)
      - Great Britain (Reel 42, Frame 160)
      - Greece (Reel 42, Frame 162)
      - Ireland (Reel 42, Frame 165)
      - Israel (Reel 42, Frame 167)
      - Japan (Reel 42, Frame 179)
      - Latin America (Reel 42, Frame 181)
      - Middle East Crisis (Reel 42, Frame 189)
      - Puerto Rico (Reel 42, Frame 194)
      - Russia (Reel 42, Frame 196)
      - Southeast Asia (Reel 42, Frame 213)
      - Tunisia (Reel 42, Frame 215)
      - United Nations (Reel 42, Frame 217)
      - Venezuela (Reel 42, Frame 235)
      - Vietnam
        - POWs (Reel 42, Frame 227)
        - General (Reel 43, Frame 14)
      - Others (Argentina - Zaire) (Reel 43, Frame 36)
      - Official International Visitors (Reel 43, Frame 75)
      - General (Reel 43, Frame 80)
    - City (Reel 43, Reel 44)
      - Albany (Reel 43)
        - Empire State South Mall (Reel 43, Frame 104)
        - General (Reel 43, Frame 134)
      - Binghamton (Reel 43, Frame 155)
      - Brooklyn (Reel 43, Frame 157)
      - Buffalo (Reel 43, Frame 162)
      - Jamestown (Reel 43, Frame 177)
      - Long Beach (Reel 43, Frame 179)
      - Mount Vernon (Reel 43, Frame 181)
      - Newburgh (Reel 43, Frame 185)
      - New Rochelle (Reel 43, Frame 189)
      - New York City
        - Police Department (Reel 43, Frame 190)
        - Special Prosecutor (Reel 43, Frame 224)
        - General
          - 1973 September-December (Reel 43, Frame 253)
          - 1972-1973 August (Reel 44, Frame 14)
      - Niagara Falls (Reel 44, Frame 164)
      - Poughkeepsie (Reel 44, Frame 168)
      - Rochester (Reel 44, Frame 172)
      - Schenectady (Reel 44, Frame 183)
      - Utica (Reel 44, Frame 191)
      - Yonkers (Reel 44, Frame 202)
      - Others (Amsterdam - White Plains) (Reel 44, Frame 208)
      - General (Reel 44, Frame 233)
    - County (Reel 44, Reel 45, Reel 46)
      - Albany (Reel 44, Frame 236)
      - Allegany (Reel 44, Frame 239)
      - Bronx (Reel 44, Frame 247)
      - Broome (Reel 44, Frame 256)
      - Cattaraugus (Reel 45, Frame 13)
      - Cayuga (Reel 45, Frame 31)
      - Clinton (Reel 45, Frame 35)
      - Columbia (Reel 45, Frame 37)
      - Cortland (Reel 45, Frame 40)
      - Delaware (Reel 45, Frame 41)
      - Dutchess (Reel 45, Frame 50)
      - Erie (Reel 45, Frame 57)
      - Essex (Reel 45, Frame 79)
      - Franklin (Reel 45, Frame 84)
      - Genesee (Reel 45, Frame 89)
      - Greene (Reel 45, Frame 92)
      - Hamilton (Reel 45, Frame 96)
      - Herkimer (Reel 45, Frame 97)
      - Kings (Reel 45, Frame 100)
      - Livingston (Reel 45, Frame 116)
      - Monroe (Reel 45, Frame 118)
      - Nassau (Reel 45, Frame 133)
      - New York (Reel 45, Frame 167)
      - Niagara (Reel 45, Frame 174)
      - Oneida (Reel 45, Frame 181)
      - Onondaga (Reel 45, Frame 185)
      - Ontario (Reel 45, Frame 187)
      - Orange (Reel 45, Frame 191)
      - Orleans (Reel 45, Frame 206)
      - Oswego (Reel 45, Frame 208)
      - Putnam (Reel 45, Frame 211)
      - Queens (Reel 45, Frame 215)
      - Rennselaer (Reel 45, Frame 223)
      - Richmond (Reel 45, Frame 225)
      - Rockland (Reel 45, Frame 229)
      - St. Lawrence (Reel 45, Frame 242)
      - Saratoga (Reel 45, Frame 244)
      - Schenectady (Reel 45, Frame 252)
      - Schoharie (Reel 45, Frame 254)
      - Seneca (Reel 46, Frame 14)
      - Steuben (Reel 46, Frame 16)
      - Suffolk (Reel 46, Frame 36)
      - Sullivan (Reel 46, Frame 71)
      - Ulster (Reel 46, Frame 78)
      - Warren (Reel 46, Frame 83)
      - Washington (Reel 46, Frame 88)
      - Wayne (Reel 46, Frame 89)
      - Westchester (Reel 46, Frame 95)
      - Others (Chemung - Yates) (Reel 46, Frame 108)
      - General (Reel 46, Frame 129)
    - Local (Reel 46, Reel 47)
      - Office of
        - Academy of Fire Science (Reel 46, Frame 135)
        - Local Government Advisory Board (Reel 46, Frame 138)
        - Community Development (Reel 46, Frame 142)
        - Fire Training (Reel 46, Frame 194)
        - General
          - 1971 October 29-1973 (Reel 46, Frame 203)
          - 1973 January 15-October 29 (Reel 47, Frame 15)
    - State (Reel 47)
      - Arizona (Reel 47, Frame 24)
      - California (Reel 47, Frame 30)
      - Delaware (Reel 47, Frame 40)
      - Georgia (Reel 47, Frame 41)
      - Hawaii (Reel 47, Frame 43)
      - Illinois (Reel 47, Frame 44)
      - New York (Reel 47)
        - Census (Reel 47, Frame 47)
        - Flags (Reel 47, Frame 59)
        - Song (Reel 47, Frame 61)
      - Michigan (Reel 47, Frame 65)
      - Missouri (Reel 47, Frame 68)
      - New Jersey (Reel 47, Frame 69)
      - New York: Bird (Reel 47, Frame 78)
      - Pennsylvania (Reel 47, Frame 88)
      - South Dakota (Reel 47, Frame 96)
      - Texas (Reel 47, Frame 97)
      - Washington (Reel 47, Frame 103)
      - Others (Alabama-Wisconsin) (Reel 47, Frame 112)
      - Interstate Committees (Reel 47, Frame 147)
    - Town (Reel 47, Reel 48)
      - Amherst (Reel 47, Frame 150)
      - Babylon (Reel 47, Frame 153)
      - Clarkstown (Reel 47, Frame 155)
      - Islip (Reel 47, Frame 157)
      - Lancaster (Reel 47, Frame 158)
      - Mount Pleasant (Reel 47, Frame 162)
      - Ohio (Reel 47, Frame 162)
      - Orangetown (Reel 47, Frame 174)
      - Ossining (Reel 47, Frame 176)
      - Portchester (Reel 47, Frame 177)
      - Rockville Centre (Reel 47, Frame 184)
      - Tarrytown (Reel 47, Frame 191)
      - Towawanda (Reel 47, Frame 193)
      - Wellsville (Reel 47, Frame 194)
      - Others (Reel 47)
        - Alden - New Hartford (Reel 47, Frame 195)
        - New Hyde Park - Yorkville (Reel 48, Frame 15)
      - General (Reel 48, Frame 49)
    - General (Reel 48)
      - New Citizens (Reel 48, Frame 51)
      - Resolutions (Reel 48, Frame 64)
      - General (Reel 48, Frame 92)
  - Health (Reel 48, Reel 49, Reel 50)
    - Department of (Reel 48)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 48, Frame 96)
      - General (Reel 48, Frame 98)
    - Hospitals (Reel 48, Reel 49, Reel 50)
      - Children's Asthma Research Institute & Hospital (Reel 48, Frame 112)
      - Coney Island Hospital (Reel 48, Frame 113)
      - Hepburn Hospital (Reel 48, Frame 119)
      - Homer Folks Tuberculosis Hospital (Reel 48, Frame 123)
      - Knickerbocker Hospital (Reel 48, Frame 129)
      - Mount Sinai Hospital (Reel 48, Frame 135)
      - Northern Westchester Hospital (Reel 48, Frame 136)
      - Ray Brook Hospital (Reel 48, Frame 137)
      - Roosewell Park Hospital (Reel 48, Frame 138)
      - St. Albans Naval Hospital (Reel 48, Frame 141)
      - Staten Island Hospital (Reel 48, Frame 148)
      - Veterans Hospital (Reel 48)
        - A-Z (Reel 48, Frame 154)
        - General (Reel 48, Frame 158)
      - West Haverstraw Hospital (Reel 48, Frame 158)
      - Others
        - Bayside Gardens Hospital - Sydenham Hospital (Reel 48, Frame 162)
        - Texas Children's Hospital - Wycoff Heights Hospital (Reel 49, Frame 14)
      - General (Reel 49)
        - Certification of Nursing Homes (Reel 49, Frame 21)
        - Steering Committee on Social Problems (Reel 49, Frame 32)
        - Hospital Costs (Reel 49, Frame 41)
        - Mobile Units (Reel 49, Frame 46)
        - Mortgage Loan Law Construction Costs (Reel 49, Frame 48)
        - Nursing Home Administers Board Examiners (Reel 49, Frame 54)
        - General (Reel 49, Frame 61)
      - Topics (Reel 49, Reel 50)
        - Abortion (Reel 49, Frame 126)
        - Acupuncture (Reel 49, Frame 159)
        - Birth Control (Reel 49, Frame 167)
        - Handicapped (Reel 49, Frame 168)
        - Kidneys (Reel 49, Frame 192)
        - Measles (Reel 49, Frame 198)
        - Sickle Cell Amenia (Reel 49, Frame 207)
        - Smoking (Reel 49, Frame 215)
        - Others (Reel 49)
          - Birth Defects - Tuberculosis (Reel 49, Frame 219)
          - Venereal Diseases (Reel 50, Frame 15)
    - General (Reel 50)
      - Ghetto Medicine (Reel 50, Frame 23)
      - Health Research Council (Reel 50, Frame 24)
      - Physician's Association & Specialists Associates (Reel 50, Frame 29)
      - Resolutions (Reel 50, Frame 30)
      - General (Reel 50, Frame 55)
  - Honorary Designation (Reel 50)
    - Chairmanship (Reel 50, Frame 86)
    - Citizenship (Reel 50, Frame 101)
    - Committee (Reel 50, Frame 103)
    - Membership (Reel 50, Frame 111)
    - Patrons (Reel 50, Frame 126)
    - Sponsors (Reel 50, Frame 128)
    - General (Reel 50, Frame 131)
  - Horse Racing (Reel 50, Reel 51)
    - Flat (Reel 50, Frame 185)
    - Hambletonian (Reel 50, Frame 188)
    - Harness (Reel 50, Frame 193)
    - Off Track Betting (OTB) (Reel 50, Frame 195)
    - Quarter Horse (Reel 50, Frame 234)
    - Thoroughbred (Reel 50, Frame 241)
    - General
      - Resolutions (Reel 50, Frame 245)
      - General (Reel 51, Frame 5)
  - Housing (Reel 51, Reel 52)
    - Division of (Reel 51)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 51, Frame 34)
      - General (Reel 51, Frame 35)
    - Construction & Repairs (Reel 51)
      - Urban Renewal (Reel 51)
        - Development Corporation (Reel 51)
          - 9 Town Project (Reel 51, Frame 40)
          - General (Reel 51, Frame 61)
        - General Rehabilitation (Reel 51, Frame 143)
        - Miscellaneous (Reel 51, Frame 149)
    - Finances (Reel 51)
      - Housing Finance Agency (Reel 51, Frame 168)
      - Mortgages (Reel 51, Frame 186)
    - Construction & Repairs (Reel 51)
      - Urban Renewal (Reel 51)
        - Model Cities (Reel 51, Frame 193)
    - Finances (Reel 51)
      - General (Reel 51, Frame 200)
    - Projects (Reel 51)
      - Battery Park City (Reel 51, Frame 206)
      - Manhattan Landing (Reel 51, Frame 215)
      - Station Plaza (Reel 51, Frame 216)
      - Stadium City (Reel 51, Frame 218)
      - Woodbrook (Reel 51, Frame 220)
      - Others
        - Ansonia Hotel - Rosedale Gardens (Reel 51, Frame 222)
        - Seven Pines - Wright Park Manor (Reel 52, Frame 14)
      - General (Reel 52, Frame 21)
    - Rent Control (Reel 52, Frame 58)
    - General (Reel 52)
      - Conversion of Rental Apartments & Cooperatives (Reel 52, Frame 79)
      - Tenant Problems (Reel 52, Frame 86)
      - Construction & Model Housing Codes (Reel 52, Frame 93)
      - Mobile Homes (Reel 52, Frame 96)
      - Resolutions (Reel 52, Frame 98)
      - Miscellaneous (Reel 52, Frame 130)
  - Insurance (Reel 52, Reel 53)
    - Department of (Reel 52)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 52, Frame 185)
      - General (Reel 52, Frame 187)
    - General (Reel 52, Reel 53)
      - Auto (Reel 52)
        - No Fault (Reel 52, Frame 194)
        - Miscellaneous (Reel 52, Frame 217)
      - Fire (Reel 52, Frame 235)
      - Health
        - Medicare (Reel 52, Frame 239)
        - Medicaid (Reel 52)
          - Payments for Abortion (Reel 52, Frame 246)
          - General (Reel 53, Frame 13)
        - National Health Institute (Reel 53, Frame 38)
        - Universal Health Plan (Reel 53, Frame 40)
        - General (Reel 53, Frame 44)
      - Resolution (Reel 53, Frame 59)
      - Miscellaneous (Reel 53, Frame 70)
  - Investigation (Reel 53)
    - General (Reel 53, Frame 100)
  - Judiciary (Reel 53, Reel 54)
    - Courts (Reel 53, Reel 54)
      - Court of Appeals (Reel 53, Frame 101)
      - Civil Court (Reel 53, Frame 105)
      - Claims (Reel 53, Frame 110)
      - County (Reel 53, Frame 111)
      - Family (Reel 53, Frame 120)
      - Narcotics (Reel 53, Frame 160)
      - Supreme (Reel 53)
        - Appellate (Reel 53, Frame 165)
        - General (Reel 53, Frame 169)
      - General (Reel 53, Reel 54)
        - Court Reform (Reel 53, Frame 194)
        - Emergency Court Program (Reel 53, Frame 213)
        - Federal (Reel 53, Frame 214)
        - Reports by Committee for Court Administration (Reel 53, Frame 215)
        - Criminal Court of New York City (Reel 54, Frame 16)
    - General (Reel 54)
      - Judicial Screening Panel (Reel 54, Frame 66)
      - Judicial Conference (Reel 54, Frame 102)
      - Legal Service Program (Reel 54, Frame 108)
      - Litigation Cases (Reel 54, Frame 110)
      - Resolutions (Reel 54, Frame 122)
      - Martin Sostre (Reel 54, Frame 153)
      - General (Reel 54, Frame 215)
  - Labor (Reel 54, Reel 55, Reel 56, Reel 57, Reel 58)
    - Department of (Reel 54, Reel 55)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 54, Frame 252)
      - Merger with the Employment Division (Reel 55, Frame 15)
      - Advisory Council on Emp. & Unemp. (Reel 55, Frame 21)
      - Insurance Labor Relations Board (Reel 55, Frame 36)
      - Division of Manpower (Reel 55)
        - Work Incentive Program (Reel 55, Frame 50)
        - General (Reel 55, Frame 57)
      - Migratory Labor (Reel 55)
        - Interdepartmental Committee (Reel 55, Frame 137)
        - General (Reel 55, Frame 169)
    - Mediation & Arbitration (Reel 55, Frame 196)
    - Minimum Wage (Reel 55, Frame 203)
    - Social Security (Reel 55, Reel 56)
      - 1972-1973 (Reel 55, Frame 204)
      - 1971 (Reel 56, Frame 17)
    - Strikes (Reel 56)
      - Aquaduct Race Track (Reel 56, Frame 48)
      - Construction Trades (Reel 56, Frame 52)
      - Lifeguards (Reel 56, Frame 60)
      - Liquor (Reel 56, Frame 61)
      - Long Island Railroad (LIRR) (Reel 56, Frame 62)
      - Longshoreman (Reel 56, Frame 197)
      - Mohawk Airlines (Reel 56, Frame 200)
      - New York City Police (Reel 56, Frame 202)
      - Railroads (Reel 56, Frame 203)
      - State Workers (Reel 56, Frame 206)
      - Telephone (Reel 56, Frame 214)
      - Others (A-Z) (Reel 56, Frame 217)
      - General (Reel 56, Frame 226)
    - Unemployment (Reel 56, Reel 57)
      - Division of Employment (Reel 56)
        - Employment of the Handicapped (Reel 56, Frame 228)
        - Employment Services (Reel 56, Frame 230)
        - General (Reel 56, Frame 236)
      - Unemployment Insurance Benefits (Reel 56, Reel 57)
        - Termination (Reel 56, Frame 241)
        - General
          - 1973 July-November (Reel 56, Frame 243)
          - 1971 January-1973 June (Reel 57, Frame 14)
          - General (Reel 57, Frame 115)
      - General (Reel 57)
        - Charts & Statistics (Reel 57, Frame 120)
        - General (Reel 57, Frame 152)
    - Workmen's Compensation (Reel 57)
      - Benefits (Reel 57, Frame 160)
      - Board (Reel 57, Frame 179)
      - General (Reel 57, Frame 206)
    - General (Reel 57, Reel 58)
      - Emergency Employment Act (Reel 57, Frame 215)
      - Pensions (Reel 58, Frame 15)
      - Resolutions (Reel 58, Frame 43)
      - Wage Claims (Reel 58, Frame 47)
      - General (Reel 58, Frame 49)
  - Law (Reel 58, Reel 59)
    - Department of (Reel 58)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 58, Frame 61)
      - General (Reel 58, Frame 62)
    - General (Reel 58, Reel 59)
      - Alcoholic Beverage Control (Reel 58, Frame 134)
      - American Flag Desecration (Reel 58, Frame 135)
      - Daylight Savings Time (Reel 58, Frame 136)
      - Domestic Relations (Reel 58, Frame 138)
      - Election Law 18 Year Old Voters (Reel 58, Frame 206)
      - Election Reapportionment
        - 1972-1973 (Reel 58, Frame 214)
        - 1971 (Reel 59, Frame 15)
      - Election Registration (Reel 59, Frame 17)
      - Election Laws (Reel 59, Frame 20)
      - Frauds (Reel 59, Frame 43)
      - Gambling (Reel 59, Frame 62)
      - Holiday (Reel 59, Frame 75)
      - Obscene Material (Reel 59, Frame 81)
      - Resolutions (Reel 59, Frame 164)
      - Sabbath Law (Reel 59, Frame 171)
      - Penal Law (Reel 59, Frame 176)
      - General (Reel 59, Frame 179)
  - Legislature (Reel 59, Reel 60)
    - Federal (Reel 59)
      - General (Reel 59, Frame 190)
      - Committees A-Z (Reel 59, Frame 195)
    - State (Reel 59, Reel 60)
      - Annual Message (Reel 59, Frame 209)
      - Committees (Reel 59, Reel 60)
        - A-Z (Reel 59, Frame 217)
        - General (Reel 59, Frame 245)
        - Special Message (Reel 59, Frame 246)
        - Special Session (Reel 60, Frame 12)
        - General (Reel 60)
          - Certificate of Intent & Allocation (Reel 60, Frame 44)
          - General (Reel 60, Frame 59)
  - Licensing (Reel 60)
    - Doctors (Reel 60, Frame 82)
    - Institutional (Reel 60, Frame 89)
    - Liquor (Reel 60, Frame 109)
    - Nurses (Reel 60, Frame 124)
    - Others (Reel 60, Frame 126)
    - General (Reel 60, Frame 134)
  - Mental Hygiene (Reel 60, Reel 61, Reel 62, Reel 63)
    - Department of (Reel 60, Reel 61, Reel 62)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 60, Frame 135)
      - Alcoholism (Reel 60, Frame 138)
      - Narcotics (Reel 60, Reel 61, Reel 62)
        - Treatment Centers
          - Cross Bay Rehabilitation Center (Reel 60, Frame 162)
          - Arthur Hill Rehabilitation Center (Reel 60, Frame 163)
          - Oddysey House (Reel 60, Frame 165)
          - Sheridan Facility (Reel 60, Frame 170)
          - Woodburne Correctional (Reel 60, Frame 172)
          - Others (Reel 60, Frame 174)
          - General (Reel 60, Frame 182)
        - New York State Council on Drugs (Reel 60, Frame 197)
        - Methadane Maintenance (Reel 60, Frame 199)
        - Prevention (Reel 60, Frame 224)
        - Rehabilitation (Reel 61, Frame 14)
        - Youthful Drug Use (Reel 61, Frame 32)
        - General
          - 1971 August-1973 December (Reel 61, Frame 58)
          - 1971 January-July (Reel 62, Frame 14)
      - General (Reel 62, Frame 32)
    - Institutions (Reel 62, Reel 63)
      - Binghamton State Hospital (Reel 62, Frame 158)
      - Buffalo State Hospital (Reel 62, Frame 161)
      - Central Islip (Reel 62, Frame 164)
      - Creedmor State Hospital (Reel 62, Frame 166)
      - Elmira Psychiatric Hospital (Reel 62, Frame 169)
      - Gowanda State Hospital (Reel 62, Frame 170)
      - Howard Park Facility (Reel 62, Frame 171)
      - Institute for Neurochemistry on Wards Island (Reel 62, Frame 173)
      - Letchworth Village (Reel 62, Frame 177)
      - Marcy State Hospital (Reel 62, Frame 181)
      - Middletown State Hospital (Reel 62, Frame 183)
      - Monroe State Hospital (Reel 62, Frame 185)
      - Queens State School (Reel 62, Frame 187)
      - Rockland State Hospital (Reel 62, Frame 189)
      - Sampson State School (Reel 62, Frame 207)
      - Suffolk State School (Reel 62, Frame 221)
      - Syracuse State School (Reel 62, Frame 227)
      - Wassaic State School (Reel 62, Frame 229)
      - Westchester State School (Reel 62, Frame 233)
      - Willowbrook
        - 1973 (Reel 62, Frame 238)
        - 1971-1972 (Reel 63, Frame 13)
      - Others (Reel 63, Frame 63)
      - General (Reel 63, Frame 88)
    - General (Reel 63)